http://www.crinfo.org/privacy-policy

Skip to main content
Sections/Site Map/Menu..
HomeBI / MBI SectionsConstructive Conflict InitiativeConstructive Conflict MOOSBI / CRInfo Knowledge BaseThings You Can Do To HelpConflict Frontiers SeminarConflict Fundamentals SeminarBeyond Intractability In ContextColleague ActivitiesAboutMissionWho We AreConflict Information ConsortiumConstructive Conflict InitiativeAbout Moving Beyond IntractabilityAbout the BI / CRInfo Knowledge BaseIntended AudiencesReprinting BI & MBI ResourcesUsing BI as a TextbookAcknowledgementsContact UsSupport Our WorkOnline LearningConstructive Conflict MOOS SeminarConstructive Confrontation ProjectThings You Can Do To Help BlogConflict Frontiers SeminarConflict Fundamentals SeminarBI / CRInfo Knowledge BaseKnowledge BaseBI / CRInfo Knowledge BaseTeaching MaterialsBeyond Intractability EssaysCRInfo Core Knowledge ArticlesCase StudiesInterviewsBook & Article SummariesPractitioner ReflectionsPeacebuilder ProfilesEducation and TrainingCareers and Funding User GuidesAffiliate ProjectsBlogsCCI BlogConstructive Conflict MOOSConflict FrontiersConflict FundamentalsThings YOU Can Do To HelpColleague ActivitiesBI in ContextNewslettersConnectSign up for the NewsletterFollow Us On Social MediaTell Us About YOUR Related WorkComment / Share IdeasContact UsDonateDonate NowSearchSearch Knowledge Base, Seminars, & BlogsSearch All of BI Plus External LinksLog In/Out
The Election, COVID, Racism, and the Constructive Conflict Initiative
Read about (and contribute to) the Constructive Conflict Initiative and its associated Blog—our effort to assemble what we collectively know about how to move beyond our hyperpolarized politics and start solving society's problems.
Updated: May 25, 2018
Because of increasingly severe and unstoppable (using conventional Captcha technology) attacks on our form and comment systems, we have been forced to implement Google's Invisible reCAPTCHA system.  Users of this part of our system are, therefore, subject to Google's Privacy Policy and Terms of Use.
This document applies to Beyond Intractability, CRInfo, and the Moving Beyond Intractability Massive Open Online Seminars operated by the Conflict Information Consortium (henceforth collectively referred to as the Consortium), located at http://www.beyondintractability.org and http://www.crinfo.org (and including any subdomains and subdirectories thereof).
Information Collection
The Consortium servers automatically record certain information about site traffic (which may include Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser types, Internet service provider (ISP) information, referring pages and search engines, platform types, date/time stamps, and other data). This information is not further linked to any personally identifiable information; it is used by the Consortium to analyze trends, administer the site, track users' movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. Additionally, the Consortium utilizes Google Analytics, which independently records traffic using a modified version of the data described above (i.e. a segment of each user's IP address is deleted to further protect users' privacy).
As a general rule and to protect user privacy we strive to keep our collection of personally identifiable information to an absolute minimum.
We do not use cookies except to authenticate "logged-in" user sessions (which are only required to post to the discussions or access seldom used, "premium content" intended for highly limited audiences).
In order to request and maintain a user account, we require users to supply a name and a valid e-mail address as well as answer a number of questions that enable us to screen out "bots" or individuals who are, in the judgment of the Consortium's Co-Directors, likely to be a disruptive, negative influence on the discussions.  That information is only accessible to Consortium's Co-Directors and immediate staff.
A user's username, as well as any material that he or she may choose to publicly provide (e.g., by creating or editing a page for publication by the Consortium, submitting a comment, editing his or her user profile, posting to the forums or discussions, or submitting information via any other mode that may not be reasonably deemed "private") may be accessible to the public, without regard for the presence of personally identifiable information.
Those who sign up for our electronic newsletter via the Newsletter Signup / Questionnaire form or the "opt in" boxes on the Contact Us, MOOS Discussion Registration, Colleague Activities Questionnaire forms can, at any time, "unsubscribe" by clicking on the unsubscribe link at the end of each Newsletter or by sending us an unsubscribe request using our Contact Us form.
We only give the Mail Chimp newsletter mailing service that we use a list of email addresses. They have no access to names or any other accompanying information except the date on which the email was added to the list and whether or not an "unsubscribe" request has been received. This means that are no "preferences" on their system to update other than unsubscribe. (Because of the way in which their system works you can, however, use their preference link to give it your name which they would not otherwise have access to and have no need for.)
We strive to ensure that the personally identifiable information that you privately provide to us (via the Inquiry for Reprints and Republications, Colleague Activities Questionnaire,  Newsletter Signup / Questionnaire, Contact Us, MOOS Discussion Registration, or any other mode that may be reasonably deemed "private") will not be made accessible to anyone other than the Consortium Co-Directors and their immediate staff without your prior consent. Such information is treated as personal correspondence that will not be disclosed to any other party without your prior consent, except when compelled to do so by law. Only broadly aggregated information about such things as general user interests is shared more widely.
All information that we collect is stored on the Consortium's servers (and backup systems) as well as local project office computers. All such storage may be maintained for an indefinite period of time.
We would be happy to freely provide anyone with a complete listing of all of the personally identifiable information that we might have on them. Simply request this information using our Contact Us form.  We will follow generally accepted principles for verifying the identity of people making such requests.
We take site security seriously and strive to keep our Drupal 7-based system fully "up-to-date." Still, given the rapidly evolving nature of today's threats to server security (threats that are beyond our ability to control), we cannot absolutely guarantee the security of the limited amount of information that we do collect.
More from
Beyond Intractability
The Intractable Conflict Challenge
Our inability to constructively handle intractable conflict is the most serious, and the most neglected, problem facing humanity. Solving today's tough problems depends upon finding better ways of dealing with these conflicts.  More...
Constructive Conflict Massive Open Online Seminar (MOOS)
Selected Recent Posts
The Peacebuilding / Constructive Confrontation Synthesis
--
Good conflict resolution skills are not just for peacebuilders--they are crucial for disputants as well. #mbi_frontiers
The Peace and Democracy-Building Continuum
--
In 1988, it looked as if democracy and peace were advancing globally. Now they are both retreating. Can we reverse that trend? #mbi_frontiers
The Risk of Large-Scale Civil Unrest and Violence in the United States
--
Are we on the brink of catastrophe...and if so, can we step back...or will we fall (or jump)? #mbi_frontiers
All CC-MOOS Posts...
Get the NewsletterCheck Out Our Quick Start Guide
Educators
Consider a low-cost BI-based custom text.
Constructive Conflict Initiative
Join Us in calling for a dramatic expansion of efforts to limit the destructiveness of intractable conflict.
Things You Can Do to Help Ideas
Practical things we can all do to limit the destructive conflicts threatening our future.
Conflict Frontiers
A free, open, online seminar exploring new approaches for addressing difficult and intractable conflicts. Major topic areas include:
Scale, Complexity, & Intractability
Massively Parallel Peacebuilding
Authoritarian Populism
Constructive Confrontation
Conflict Fundamentals
An look at to the fundamental building blocks of the peace and conflict field covering both “tractable” and intractable conflict.
Beyond Intractability / CRInfo
Knowledge Base
Home / Browse | Essays | Search | About
BI in Context
Links to thought-provoking articles exploring the larger, societal dimension of intractability.
Colleague Activities
Information about interesting conflict and peacebuilding efforts.
Disclaimer: All opinions expressed are those of the authors and do not necessarily reflect those of Beyond Intractability or the Conflict Information Consortium.
Beyond Intractability
Unless otherwise noted on individual pages, all content is...
Copyright © 2003-2019 The Beyond Intractability Project
c/o the Conflict Information Consortium
All rights reserved. Content may not be reproduced without prior written permission.
Guidelines for Using Beyond Intractability resources. Inquire about Affordable Reprint/Republication Rights.
Citing Beyond Intractability resources.
Photo Credits for Homepage, Sidebars, and Landing Pages
Contact Beyond Intractability
Privacy Policy
The Beyond Intractability Knowledge Base Project Guy Burgess and Heidi Burgess, Co-Directors and Editors
c/o Conflict Information Consortium
UCB580, University of Colorado, Boulder, CO, 80309, USAContact Form
Powered by Drupal
